{
    "id": "ddaf1bee88ce477093b2d6741454dc97",
    "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Where could the horse ......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5dead130d794a538968fd3721c747ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Circumstances ....................... him to leave school when he was just ten.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forced",
                "have forced",
                "were forcing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9c8ec98a98e47a89d9cdc096ee4dbba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He heard that his brother .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "has arrived",
                "had arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "326f26642bad4e579f34c201b5eb8979"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... my homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "completed",
                "have completed",
                "had completed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9eff326c9f754f98a7a27161e594994e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... before I reached his place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a6558ed6d197496f833696da2d0f3e81"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ..................... .. their homework by now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will finish",
                "will have finished",
                "will be finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d809a81a92354409baee914f0598af41"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shakespeareâ€™s plays ..................... into nearly all languages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have translated",
                "have been translated",
                "were being translated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b4a0bc8720842dd9744f13824d364d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Indians ..................... .. skilled mathematicians for thousands of years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have been",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8a5147bd22544d29d312f13d08cf4f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys performed all the tasks we ...................... for them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have planned",
                "had planned",
                "were planning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e7fca6ca7d74de3b418ba866e5a6863"
        },
        {
            "question": "He forgave his enemies who ....................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have wronged",
                "had wronged",
                "had been wronged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eec851cd3b86459fa3ea7ae39c3274d3"
        }
    ]
}